right
for driving it's not really focused it's
only focus is there any key flick on the
screen and focus it it's doing a little
better it's doing a little better
yeah it's confuse you know apple's
algorithms aren't necessarily trained on
their autofocus model isn't necessarily
tested on
- sick Khem fig what's up control hey
Andy can come all the abstracts you know
q-tip but his Kamala's kam a al check it
out
q-tip
does anyone say anything now you got a
handy that's about it Hey
why don't you tell people what you're
doing we're driving into San Diego this
is like fleeing the dystopia part two I
already moved to San Diego but we're
driving a Penske truck rental 12-footer
packed with furniture and things I've
been living real aesthetically in San
Diego sleeping on the hardwood floor you
know real Steve Jobs mode but now we're
furniture in nice things you know we're
gonna comfort down and the cameraman is
my partner in crime
our life partner in life you know not
like that my partner in life is driving
a Fiat ahead of us should have poured of
the Oakland pilot to the you hope you
know I am minutes I want to talk on this
about a pronto done a I we just comment
on AI for each other Bluetooth
transmitter which is common I for trucks
and I'm really looking forward to being
able to eventually hopefully drive a
rental Penske truck that has a pronto
system built in
we got cruise control on this truck but
you know Penske is going to be the one
to do it alright we can talk about truck
rental companies and we can talk about
how at u-haul is trash u-haul wasted an
hour and a half of my time and I got a
charge back $600 on my car in fact
$1,200 from my card because the first
600 was for our truck reservation in
Berkley rolled up to the u-haul the
reservation time you're supposed to be
able to you know unlock the car from
your app but I clicked the unlock button
picked up and I got of some unknown air
please call John he called John straight
to voicemail
straight to voicemail so like okay
there's a lot of you all locations go
ahead and reserve in Oakland so I
reserved in Oakland and this is uh this
is a human picked up assistant the
automated pick up so that Sutter you all
franchise and reservation 5:30 the
franchise says that listed hours close
to 6:00 on Monday
roll up at 5:30 doors lock no one's in
there I call their phone number I can
see through the window there phone
ringing inside and of course no one's in
there so we flipped off the security
camera outside about 15 times and I
called Penske Penske truck rentals are
professionals I call them in six minutes
told them where I was told him where I
was
and got my truck got my truck reserved
and we rolled up roll up to Home Depot
and got got a Penske truck the customer
service rep was beyond professional and
efficient so yeah if you're gonna rent a
truck you all don't give them your
business gift and ski truck rentals your
business
that's an official statement I'm tonight
or tomorrow night at the latest Thursday
I will be creating an array of anti
u-haul internet properties we're talking
comms we're talking dorks we're talking
thousands that were they killed with
them yeah we're talking we're talking
thousands of fake Yelp accounts spewing
the truth the truth you know
if you make the internet bots and you
spread you spread falsehood that's bad
but if you make internet bots and you
spread truth I would say that's Noble
that feels pretty I've seen so far
[Music]
yeah so it's
it's it's it's up to us you know you can
call you all support you can get all
angry you know you can talk I'm gonna
I'm really I'm really caller support and
I'm gonna make my way up to manager
James speaker manager I must speak to
your manager and you'll be able to maybe
get up maybe get a message but you can
enact change through that because
because you know what really needs to
hear your message are prospective you
all customers is unfortunate evil as is
brands that's good name you've all and
people probably don't even necessarily
go on the internet before giving you our
reservation because then just like you
all I see them around town but there
there are many such cases of people
being kind of just left left out in the
water there when they're trying to pick
up their u-haul and I really want to
make sure that these people's story is
mine and the many others including her
so we might get u-haul scam store we'll
put a fake 501 3 C logo you know
Better Business Bureau all the all the
like logos you can put on the website
Kelly deliver us Kelly Blue Book
approved to Consumer Reports affiliated
yeah
an American flag
but we should also translate the same
yeah and you can click on your flag and
get the dominant language in your
country live translated on a website is
everyone needs to know part of the
Longshoremen's Union
I think the units could be in on this
there's definitely I'm sure the unions
have the same and many other reasons to
also also oppose you all
angrily sips water
this guy's gonna flush flush these
thoughts out highway five is beautiful
California's beautiful the Central
Valley is pristine you know I really I
really want to go on an El Camino rail
trip and stop by all of the missions
[Music]
my favorite mission is in Soledad
California which is maybe an hour south
of Monterey it's it's one of the most
call pristine untouched other than by
agriculture in all areas of California
Soledad California there's a mission
nuestro de Soleil that Catholic mission
of course Spanish missionaries set it up
hundreds of years ago it's a beautiful
place I highly recommend it
on that same trip you can also stop by
the pinnacles National Monument which is
like this part dedicated to these huge
ass rocks which is why it's called
pinnacles there's literal pinnacle rocks
it's fun it's fun place playful families
if young people ready for old people
great for everyone everyone likes rocks
if you don't like rocks I don't know I
don't know what to say please swear on
this oh yeah you if you don't like
rocks lucky if you don't like rocks
yeah
it was someone who there are no rocks
Arkansas
there's no rocks in Arkansas I don't
think so what is there
[Music]
I guess there's this rock underneath but
rock above
I'd intended you know Arkansas corn
God told you this personally
now
I am into it in you know an act by our
Creator however I don't know God you can
just as just wrist tape and Nature Made
Arkansas have no rocks we can speculate
on the reason and that's art it's our
duty today everyone can just appreciate
that Arkansas has no rocks and has a lot
of corn and I really can appreciate that
effect and mr. John Tatum sped said
speaking of beautiful places check out
Swami's Beach and the meditations are
going to get dusty
hey with the meditation what meditation
garden I'm gonna go to the meditation
garden I'll bring my ex I'll bring my
extra-long yoga mat and Papa Lotus
one appellate in the truck
yeah
a lot of things they know things need to
be moved you know
chuck's our trucks are important
and companies like pronto about AI are
doing wonders for trucking and making it
safer more efficient in the end result
will be cheaper goods for everyone
cheaper goods cost of shipping drops
you know truckers have an eight-hour
limit lose all sedition Li like a weekly
limit for safety and it's a good I think
it's a good rule however we can use
technology to push that so that you know
the goal of a fully autonomous trucks
that's 80 years off but if we use driver
assistance systems in trucks and cars
alike can make driving better can make
it safer and easier to drive for longer
times longer distances and that's a good
thing
it's a good thing
polymerase we got you
well we're update number back down to
three we were up to eat I think your
aunt about truck needs goes away
chucking rocks trucking all the rock
eaters left and now only only the true
believers are left that was that was
intended as a test as a filter
hey this highway hasn't been adopted yet
really I think Rockhopper Holdings LLC
mind a venture side hustle which
eventually will become a made hustle
will adopt essentially this section of
highway five it's pretty beautiful
surprising it was adopted it yet wonder
how much that costs adopted a heroin
yeah like we gotta call the one eight
six six
adopt-a-highway and that was listed on
the sign dr. Heidi think you just give
them a like a cash me and I'm like they
take care of it here you know it's
probably irritating them cash and you
get a year to adopt it for a certain
amount of time and people probably renew
you know the government's kind of nice
like annual recurring revenue plan
they're both taxes and adopt-a-highway
well what if you adopt a highway and the
government's just like blazing
inefficient their highways since 30
millisecond company doesn't guarantee
like inverse effective like
like you your company looks worse yes
the highway highway yeah I wouldn't
adopt a shitty Highway section it's sad
because the highlight sections that are
the shadiest are the ones that most need
adopting what's the project children
what's my battery at
my battery dies
but as we all know the last 1% is the
longest percent
yeah this desktop wallpaper were the
scenery a bit like a drive-in to like
Windows 98 right now
yeah we're driving through the desert
and those night and I mean XP as the
experience exp has the grassy plain what
did was deaf
I don't even remember I just
remember the Vista taskbar you know aqua
aqua theme they were like wait we need
to make windows look like max what a max
look like aqua looks like you're
underwater they still have the swish
yeah they just swish yeah yeah yeah oh
yeah but uh Wow max were like waiting in
a warm Southern California pool that was
there aqua design Vista was more like
waterboarding
[Music]
we got our back 1 2 3
he's from Russia apparently hey I love
Russia
please
but I think of Russia I think the
Modesto California was snow on
it's a great truck we got that AC
twelve 12 volt power where USB
I'll show you you almost have this
good air bags over safe yeah we're safe
jeez the worst thing about airbags being
deployed is they smell bad really
what are they smell like
the stylist air
possible that's been like compressed so
it like is accelerated as
like it's like becoming stale there's
other like they have other probably
other gases in their bag other than just
peer you know care oceanic air it's
probably like some other in there
that just affects the smell be at like
you crash your car you're fine
but then you're like you smell a mixture
of like total engine and air bag air
about the designer air market do you
think that's gonna become a begginer
life designer
yeah you know like the Chinese and all
these people with these countries that
they don't have clean air how do you use
the designer air and I get like a like
an air tank like for scuba diving you
just sit in your uh hey Lily if they can
made stuff thinking they can and like it
compressed air tank not look like as
much of a medical device as it does
right now so now we make it look like a
dual cabin yeah if we make if we make
the compressed air look like a tool and
in fact if you maybe you sell it in
disposable like containers that would
even be better make sure that you are
recyclable in some way though or else
people will be concerned about the waste
the people are showing us love
okay yeah sure why don't you wanna you
started this why don't you get it to the
point you bring the designer hair market
to San Diego
I feel like LA needs it more than we do
yeah I mean you can start the business
in San Diego and make him sell it on the
salad and on Venice Beach next to the
next to the cannabis dealer
yeah you know that's that's definite
that in my work
- it must these people are high they're
probably kind of gullible yeah they want
some designer hair
I want to call them earbuds a good idea
I can pull it if you call them user
space pods especially because they're
totally different category air - putt
well that settles that I'm gonna take my
entire all of my savings in two thousand
dollars yeah I can get a nice line of
credit look every almost every
successful entrepreneur I know at some
point or still does have like a shitload
of credit card in credit card debt is
bad but if you like clearly it's like
you know spending it's unfortunately
it's the most accessible force of debt
for for like independence of all
business owners result proprietors
trying to try and get something off the
ground I know plenty of people with like
tens of thousands dollars of credit card
debt that they're worth 25 billion on
paper it's just it's all full of like
Silicon Valley stock options and they
can't they can't like exercise them
without like out of the front of tax
bill so you can get a loan for the tax
bill but it's still kind of suss and it
takes a lot of takes a lot of time and
energy and still risky so
yeah and I think we're gonna make our
money is probably by simplifying
electronic payments I think that's what
there's a lot of people trying to do
that man I know I know but we're gonna
do it and a semi-legit gotta wait I'm
gonna use QR codes yeah all of China
we're gonna bring WeChat to America
yeah we need to make America sweet chat
sounds like returning with them it
sounds like I don't really want to
compete with Facebook and all these
other people that like really know how
messaging works to the extent that I can
benefit the message in speeders by
making messaging BOTS and like I don't
know some like retro IRC interfaces for
for modern messaging apps I'll be nice
and here the Japanese are big and
illiberal point up the Japanese are
being a web link we know I'm gonna look
into this go uh someone in the chat go
look like a Japanese website find out
you know what they're like they oughta
slap one find out which Japanese website
web 1.0 and it was a little more
functional you know I didn't have a
loading spinner when you loaded the page
you know your links were links you could
right click them and copy the link you
you know there's a lot of benefits to
doing things web 1.0 I think I've got a
hybrid approach is good things can look
prettier in web 2.0 released all three
miles take exit 407 for California 33
toward 7 Villa Gilroy
right up to the counter straps to the
counter and we'll only put the phone
down if they say no video recorded in
here we can allege there seem to be
right there
looks like a CHP truck I've never seen
one of those we have the ischium lovers
oh yeah you know that because they can
fill them up with like a bunch of
candidates a bunch of lead bags and they
can spend they and they cease yes you
know it's a weird in certain parts of
California CHP like that these white
cars I don't know like
what the distinction is like what is
like you know once they should be like
what a distinction and sees me yeah like
why do you get a white squad guard like
certain parts of his name
yeah I didn't know how that works and
you know how the statesman's are our
money are we going to China someone's
desk girl in San Diego we're driving
there half-a-mile tickets at 4:07 by 1
million 33 toward 7 Villa Gilroy the
infrastructure project this world needs
is a giant freeway across the Pacific
from California to China
oh the Korean take exit for us all
right
abort periscope aboard periscope we got
to call him in a quarter-mile